

# Vladimir Djukanovic

Software Engineer

♥ UPPSALA, 754 33, SWEDEN

### 

I am a graduate student in software engineering, currently working at Vizrt in Stockholm, Sweden.

I am very ambitious, devoted and passionate about software engineering and projects related to modern ICT. I am always striving for new challenges, obtaining extensive knowledge in state of the art technologies and giving my best because I want to advance, and gain valuable experience.

## Employment history

Full Stack Engineer at Vizrt Sweden AB, Stockholm

October 2017 - Present

Full stack engineer with a focus on front-end development of various applications offered by Vizrt. Technologies that are included are JAVA (GWT, Smart GWT), .NET(C#), Javascript, testing and test automation using Selenium, Cucumber, JUnit, MOQ.

Junior Front end Developer at BILD studio, Podgorica

June 2015 - September 2015

Building beautiful web applications in state of the art technologies. Technologies that are included in everyday work are Angular JS, Node.js, JQuery, MongoDB, Sass.

## Education

Software Engineering, Mälardalen University, Västerås September 2016 – June 2017

Studying at this university was a big step in professional and personal development. The significant improvement in different areas through a professional environment and shared knowledge with the focus on state of the art technologies and industries are just some of the benefits of studying at Mälardalen.

Bachelor of Computer Science, University Mediterranean, Podgorica September 2014 - July 2017

Studying at Mediterranean university was an enriching experience which provided me with an extensive knowledge in many areas of Computer Science and software engineering. It was a great guide to my personal and professional development.

## Courses

Software Engineering 2: Project Teamwork, Mälardalen University November 2016 – January 2017

Software Development for Real-Time Systems, Mälardalen University April 2017 – June 2017

#### Details

Uppsala, 754 33,

Sweden 0769006673

vladimir.djukanovic@yahoo.com

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

1995-06-13 Podgorica

NATIONALITY

Montenegrin

### Social Profiles

Github

LinkedIn

#### Skills

**JAVA** 

Javascript

AngularJs

C#

Testing and test automation (JUnit, Moq, Selenium, Cucumber)

Scrum

PHP

Version Control

Communication and collaboration

Organizational skills

### Languages

Serbo-croatian, Bosnian, Montenegrin

English

Swedish